(Penny:)Nothing.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I'm surprised
you'd choose to go to a pub.
(Sheldon:)At our committee meeting,
(Sheldon:)Amy made a motion
for a picnic in a park,
(Sheldon:)but I tacked so many amendments
on that thing
(Sheldon:)it sank like a lead balloon.
(Amy:)I then suggested a pub.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, which I was
initially skeptical of until
(Sheldon:)I saw online that they serve
Yorkshire pudding.
(Leonard:)You don't even like
(Sheldon:)No, it's yucky,
(Sheldon:)but informing people about
the history of Yorkshire
(Sheldon:)is yummy, yum-yum.
(Amy:)After a lively debate,
(Amy:)that proposal passed
by a two-zero margin.
(Leonard:)Nice to see a busy couple
(Leonard:)keep the spark
of bureaucracy alive.
(quiet laugh)
(Sheldon:)Ignore them, Amy.
They're just jealous
(Sheldon:)because they'll never have
a relationship as good as ours.
(Penny:)Isn't this when he says
"bazooka" or something?